noobfeed.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy

## NOOBFEED PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy is here to tell you how we are going to obtain and use personal details about all users that visit this site. If you would like to contact us about anything you read here we would be happy to discuss it with you: contact@noobfeed.com.

When creating an account on NoobFeed you are required to provide us with the following information:

User Name and Password – Both used to help make and manage your account. Email Address – Used to help confirm your account before using the site. It will also be used to send you announcements and updates about the site depending on whether you agree to this or not when asked. 

When logged in to your account all information posted by you will be identified under your user name. When you are not logged in to your account all information posted by you will be identified as anonymous.

### USER PROFILES

Upon the creation of your account you may add various thing’s to your account by choice, this includes but is not limited to: your name, your gender, your age and various images or photographs. Everything you decide to add to your account will be displayed for all to see. We stress that you are not under any circumstances required to provide this information unless you choose to.

### WEBSITES AND FORUM POSTS

Every single piece of information you post on both the main website and the community forums will be directly identifiable to your account. We are not responsible for anything you may choose to post and we advise all members to follow the rules of the website stated in our Terms of Use and be careful of posting anything that you are worried may slip into the wrong hands.

### PRIVATE MESSAGING

If you would like to send another user a personal message the person receiving the message will see your user name and any other information contained within that message. They will not see anything else through our personal messaging system.

### OTHER WEBSITES

We may link to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us and follow their own sets of rules and have their own privacy policy.

### COMPETITIONS

If we have any competitions on the main website or in the community forums we may ask for further personal information from you. This is not compulsory.

### THIRD PARTIES

We will try our best to keep your information out of the hands of any third parties.

We may provide them with anonymous data figures from our website but they will never contain any of your personal information.

We may use a third party also if we require them to help us with any part of our site, help such as hosting for our forums or sending out newsletters. In this case we may need to pass certain bits of information on to these third parties to aid us in our process.

We may use a third party also if we require them to help us with any part of our site, help such as hosting for our forums or sending out newsletters. In this case we may need to pass certain bits of information on to these third parties to aid us in our process.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. When you view ads on our site, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your browser by the ad-serving company. In addition, the ad-serving companies may use web beacons to help manage and optimize our online advertising. The information collected by the ad-serving companies may be used to target ads to you on this site and on other sites that you visit. To "opt-out" of these ad-serving cookies and web beacons, please click here. <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

### COOKIES, WEB BEACONS AND WEB LOGS

We set a temporary session cookie whenever you visit the site. It will be deleted when you close your browser. If you merely read the site without logging in, you may instruct your browser to deny this cookie.

When you log into the site, we may set a persistent cookie, which will allow us to recognize you as an existing registered user and avoid the need to log into the site again. These cookies may last for up to 30 days. You may clear these cookies in your browser after a session in which you have logged in.

Our web pages may also contain an electronic file called a web beacon that allows us to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies.

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. We store this data in files called web logs. These web logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the site you came from, the next site you visit and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

None of the data collected through web beacons, cookies or web log data provides us with any personal information about you. We use this data on an aggregated basis to analyze how our users are interacting with the site and to customize your experience, such as by remembering your preferences and showing you content that you have tagged. If you are logged in to the site, we could associate information about your site usage that is collected by cookies, web beacons and web logs with your user account. However, we don't do this on an individual basis other than in cases of suspected abuse or illegal behavior.

### THE LAW

We have the right at any time to share your information with the law or investigators if we feel that illegal activity has taken place on your account in any way, shape or form. This includes anything that is stated in our Terms of Use. It also includes providing extra information to the law if you’re involved in any form of legal process and the thing’s you’ve done on this site could be used as evidence.

### PROTECTION

We aim to do everything in our power to keep all your personal information safe and secure. There is however no 100% guaranteed way of us promising you that as is the case with every single other website found on the internet. If you feel at any point your account has been illegally accessed or tampered with in any way please contact us: contact@noobfeed.com.

### TERMINATION

If at any time you would like to cancel your account with NoobFeed at any time please send us an email to contact@noobfeed.com and we will terminate it as soon as possible. Upon the termination of your account we may still keep certain bits of information that we deem appropriate, the information we keep will continue to be subject to the terms of our privacy policy.

### SELLING

If we ever sell our business in whole or in part some or all of your information may be transferred over as a result.

### CHANGES TO OUR POLICY

If we make any changes to our privacy policy we will state so in this section. We reserve the right to edit any piece if information found here if and when we see fit to.
